ladies and gentlemen put your hands
together for Ali sadik
[Applause]
hey I want to I want to start by doing
this first and this is very sincere very
sincere I want to thank y'all for
showing up to see
me I do
it is a it is a honor cuz one y' y'all
like me y'all like me right and y'all
show me a lot of love and y'all love me
now I I need this from y'all I really do
cuz U that family of mine is
different yeah you can't be a king in
your own castle let me tell you
something if you men let me tell you I'm
talking to men men if you are not
handy you might want to learn to fix
something
cuz for some reason when you not handy
you get totally disrespected man people
don't love me in my house cuz I can't
fix
stuff and but I'm I'm honest I'm honest
about not being able to fix stff I don't
say I can I am not the one that you call
when you want something to fix I am the
one you call when you want something
new when you want something new I am
your man if you want something fixed
call somebody else my mama have two
washing drers in her house right now
because she call me
first and he folks know I'm not hand my
mama called me and said baby something
is wrong with my wash and dry it's not
running and it's beeping and I came over
there I showed up like it was a
bomb momy is beeping get the people get
another
one now I'm thinking when they bring the
new washer and dryer
they going to take the old
one they just drop it off they just
leave it anything I'm on the phone with
the
plumber hey I need somebody down here my
mama got a new wash and dryer now back
story my sister comes in I heard my
sister come in and my sister take every
opportunity to make me look
bad my sister come in I'm in the back
and then I notice the beeping stop
I come in I'm talking to my mom say what
she
do my sister went in the
dryer open the dry open the lint
thing clean the lint thing I closed
[Applause]
it my sister going to say hey I am my
mama's only son stop coming over
[Applause]
when you not hand it you you will be
embarrassed in your house when you not
handy cuz let me tell you something
fellas what you don't want is other men
to come in your house and fix
up I get
home my garage door won't go down I went
and hit the
thing nothing happening I hit my I went
to the truck and got the remote
nothing's happening I call a
number calling people the man come over
and I tell the man I say hey um brother
you need anything I'm going to be right
in the house just knock on the door and
I'm going to come out here I don't even
clo do you understand I ain't even close
the door like I'm my heel is right there
the man and knocked on the door I said
no I know the brother don't want nothing
already I said what's up bro he said oh
I'm done
and you about to be
mad I said you done he said yeah um hit
that thing real
quick nothing happening right a nothing
hit your remote nothing happening right
you see this little rope right
[Applause]
here don't hit
[Music]
it and he going to keep doing it too
look you can put it on you can you can
put it
[Applause]
[Music]
off you want you want to do it I don't
need to practice I saw what you
did he said let me tell you a part you
about to be mad
about according to company
policy since I came over here that's
135 I said you damn sure right I'm mad
at them
it's something about when you not handy
and when you not handy you can't even go
into things that you heard before you
ever heard the saying the customer is
always right H not if you don't know
what you
doing I'm living in this little gated
community right I have noticed that I
have not even been considered for yard
of the month not one time been over
there 7even years ain't nobody even
considered me now I'm I'm blaming this
on my yard man this ain't racist My Yard
Man Carlos he just he just happened to
be
Mexican I come out there Carlos hey bro
let me tell you something bro you
cutting my grass too low that's why I'm
not winning car say no no my friend I'm
cutting it right I'm like Carlos listen
to
me you cutting my grass too low I need
it this high if you can't do that don't
come back around here
Carlos Carlo's gone for 4 weeks
[Applause]
grass just high on Safari out there
grass just
[Applause]
high so I decide I'm going to go get a
lawnmower I'mma cut it
myself man let me let me tell y'all
something I didn't know that a lawn mow
didn't come already assembled you got to
assemble it and why they don't give you
that first can of
gas with the laama how they know you got
a gas can fellas let me tell you
something get your gas can cuz that long
M was way heavier once you put that gas
in and try to get back on the
truck don't laugh at me dog I said I
wasn't handed don't do don't don't lean
back on me dog I told you I wasn't handy
boy they always try to make you feel bad
I tell you
boy this man helped me get the L on the
truck right I get it home my neighbor
helped me get it off now I'm about to
cut my grass about to cut this grass
yeah now it's some things that I've
noticed that Carlos has when he cut the
grass long
pants boots on long sleeve shirts some
around his neck glasses on big
hat now I don't I didn't know that you
needed all that but I'm telling you
these uh these shorts and these Gucci
flipflops just ain't working out here
but it rough it rough man it's rough boy
it's
rough that first that first trip down
was rough I'm trying to tell you that
second trip that second trip I noticed
why Carlos got that hat but that son was
following
me I start huming for no
reason I'm talking about sun on top of
me all on my neck I'm it's crazy
[Applause]
right third trip down I ain't going to
lie I ain't going to lie y'all I was
about to stop I was about to stop mowing
I'm about to stop M but Carlos come on
the
street he coming down like Minister
[Applause]
Society got me all around I call you
crazy as hell
Carlos Carlos turned that corner I I
went in the
house I don't know how
long I'm in the house B it took me a nap
I don't know how long I'm there I am
awakened by my lawn mow being on my lawn
more come
on I don't even rush out there if
somebody's stealing it I just look out
the
blinds I look out
there it's
Carlos moreing that grass I came out
there and I H
Carlos gave caros $150 I said you can
keep that lawn mow if you want it I
don't need it
I don't need it I'm never I'm
never you don't even worry about it that
sun whoop me into shape you know what
I'm saying I am a house negro I see what
this
[Applause]
is It's a thing it's things about me I'm
honest about who I am now what you're
not going to do is tell me what to do in
my house cuz they and they cuz they
disrespect me in my house I'm trying to
tell you I be trying to fix something
I'm in the garage F to fix something cuz
my light switch is tripping I see my son
hovering around with his
phone I said what what you doing you
trying to record me or something he said
about no I've been a signed to
you I said boy you electrocute yourself
one time and all of a sudden somebody
watching over over
you wasn't even my fault I told them
folk not to turn that Brak on I said
it and folks come messing with me I'm in
the house man in the house minding my
business I look up I see that my air
filter is a little
dirty as I'm looking at the air filter
dou a going to come out to about hey
don't touch that air filter Raul coming
over here Thursday first of all Raul
don't pay no goddamn bills in this house
you don't tell me about no damn what ra
is
[Applause]
doing everybody leave everybody leave
the house right everybody leave as soon
as they gone tool belt
on going to change this air filter I get
my ladder and I go up there now I have
changed regular air filters before
regular water
where you lash the thing and it come
down
straight now this one come down to the
side and y'all I'm I'm a I'm a trained
fighter when something come in my head
I'm boom now what you can't do is do
that on the ladder I'm going just say
you can't do that on the
[Applause]
ladder I hard step I'm off the ladder
let me tell y'all something
man when you falling man ain't
nothing man I need need to put a lantern
or some paintings on my wall or
something it's
[Applause]
just I hit my head on the top of the
door
okay I'm out I'm
out I'm
out I am
awakened by the garage coming up I said
oh they back
[Applause]
why you come in the house messing with
me doublea came
in why is your eyes so
glassy I say glassy no no no I I was
watching TV it was so sad it was so sad
something happen the TV ain't even on I
I cut it off it was just too
sad why is your ear bleeding I said yeah
I'm bleeding I'm
bleeding a no ain't no I bleed Ain no I
bleed walked
off came back to my come get your
concussed ass in this car
why why you say I got a concussion why
is there a ladder in my kitchen I said a
ladder hold my hand hold my
[Applause]
hand is a
shame so I know I'm I'm not handy but
what I do is
this I utilize the people in my life
that is my uncle is a handy man he's a
handy man do you what I'm understanding
so when something go wrong with my house
I call him why are you going to ridicule
me for calling you and you a handy
man and I'm I'm gonna say this man
Listen People handy men is sitting here
when a non-handed man
call you we don't need your ridicule we
have already submitted you know what I'm
saying we come with money already in our
hand here just
[Applause]
just I call
Mom he answer the
phone I said uh he said what you got
going on nephew I said man something in
my house is wrong he said what you got
you know that's what handed me and say
what what you got I said man um the
thing what goddamn thing I said who you
yelling at I'm not just going to say the
thing I'mma describe
[Applause]
it I'mma describe
it I said the thing that makes the water
hot
[Applause]
he said the hot water heater I said if
that's the technical name of
[Applause]
it what's wrong with it I said it's not
blue at the bottom like it normally
is he said because the pilet is out you
going to have to light the pilet I said
no I ain't like no pilot
why would I like a pilot he said why you
can't like the pilot I said because I
read the
directions he said that don't make no
God damn sense if you read directions
why you can't like the pastor you don't
understand on the directions it said
boom
explode and there's a man on there
running with fire
coming from his
body how did that
[Applause]
happen
fire now contractors have been in my
home before I know how contractor
supposed to walk in your home my uncle
came to my house I don't know he walked
in sorry
[Applause]
are you aware that I called your company
and not your cell
phone I am a customer sir I have an
[Applause]
invoice he talking about where this
at I say still aggressive are we yel
review is about to be
[Applause]
bad so the way I want him to come in my
house I want him to come through the
garage because it's easy come through
the
garage walk in when you come in my house
there a you walk in it's a closet right
there there a little closet right there
then you go a little
further it's a room right there then you
go a little further it's the laundry
room right and then you go a couple more
steps at the laundry room it's the
little junk that go to the attic right
the little step ladder thing that come
to the attic now I know y'all Wonder
like he don't know what that is I I
don't mess with my addict I'm not no
addict type
person I ain't never been in that attic
that attic is spooky I never been in
there I don't see a reason for me to be
going in my attic now
um let let me tell you how disconnected
I am with this attic right I heard
something Coss around in my attic the
other day and I turned the heat up to
96 it's going to die whatever's up there
is going to suffocate and it's going to
die and the housekeeper going to go up
there and get it I'm not messing with
it makes no sense for me to be up
[Applause]
there just think about it whatever's up
there whatever's up there you coming up
the steps you you vulnerable it's going
to pounce down on you now you didn't
fell down the steps now you dead see how
that work you ain't thinking pass your
shoes now well the um where the little
attic steps in they in right in front of
the laundry and that's why I'm at in the
laundry room doing laundry it's a skill
um I'm separating my clothes I'm putting
wo light in my
delicates and as my uncle walking up the
steps all I said was hey read the
directions that man said man
you I've been doing this for your
ass was even born I'm like well things
could have
[Applause]
changed he up there right I hear him up
there he didn't click that thing like
six times I heard him about I say now
wait one damn minute
now I raise direction that thing you
supposed to click that thing once or
twice and you supposed to wait it's a
waiting period and then I hear him again
I say now that's 12 clicks that is 12
clicks I count them that's 12 clicks man
I'm thinking we all right because I
don't hear no gas next thing I
hear 3 seconds later
boom my uncle has been blown down the
steps and he is on fire like the
[Applause]
man he's on fire do you understand me
that man's on
[Applause]
fire with my quick thinking cuz I'm a
quick
thinker I put my uncle out with wood
[Applause]
like my uncle is on the ground
singed with wood light on him he going
to look up at
me your different I told you to
read the directions I told him I said it
I said it out loud
read the
directions exactly what I
[Applause]
said and sometime I be feeling like I'm
in I'm in the I'm in the
wrong
family cuz they not utilizing me for the
things that I'm good at like I'm I'm I
come from a pretty tough family like and
I'm talking about everybody think they
tough but it's a
it's a difference when because I this
this how this how I judge it I judge it
according to my uncle ma Black Mac Black
Mac different man this is the epitome of
tough cuz he taught me this cuz a lot of
men in here probably think they tough
but are you pulling out your own teeth
[Applause]
tough yeah that's
different this levels the
toughness man I'm nine I'm
nine I'm in the living room watching
bonanza with my uncle ma my uncle Mac
out of nowhere said God damn it my
goddamn too hurt go get the pliers I
said go get the
pliers I'm not I know it's a lot of
steps before go get the
pliers goggling with warm salt water
that's
one yeah putting some EPS you know put
EP on on it I'm talking about um a
dentist that's
Dennis my uncle Alfred come in with some
needle noose Plies and say you
ain't going to do with him gave
them to him and I'm sitting
there my uncle Mac didn't even leave the
living
room he just with them fly and I'm and
listen to me listen to me I'm not
talking about one of them little teeth
at the bottom or one of them ones on the
side I'm talking about one of them ones
in the back that's attached to your
spleen and your
brain and your whole core
existence you say I'm talking about yeah
you supposed to have a surgent and be
sleep when they get one of these
out man that man one of the most
excruciating sounds I ever heard with
them need he over
there snatch that tooth out of his mouth
Gogle with some whiskey and then put a
whole bunch of BC pow and pass out I
said
boy I don't even know how he got all
that BC pow in his mouth you know one BC
pow to get in the middle of your tongue
you won't swallow for two
[Applause]
weeks I'm sitting there like ooo I am in
the wrong family this is
[Applause]
not it's
crazy you got to be handy and I and I
would like CU I I've done some things
cuz I'm not hand I've done some real
weak things I see some Hispanic men in
here I would like to take this
opportunity to apologize to all Hispanic
men around the world for some real weak
I was doing about 25 years ago I
live in Houston I live in this little
Hispanic neighborhood before I move
where I live at now and um I know
Mexican men are very helpful
no matter what the news be talking about
these people are helpful they help you
with anything somebody need to be fixed
they going to come and help you out you
know what I'm saying and that's what
they do now I know they help you now I'm
taking advantage of this
[Applause]
help man you know when I lived in this
neighborhood I never took my truck to
the
mechanic never I would never take my
truck to the mechanic I would just go
outside I would just go outside and lift
my hood up
[Applause]
and be waiting for my neighbor Jose to
come
outside Jose come out my friend what's
wrong with my friend I'm
[Applause]
know once Jose come over there and call
Manuel and call I just go in the
house with the
ladies I been now e that's that's spicy
I don't like that that's spicy
I would like to
apologize you don't really know how
people in your family feel about you you
know until you hear them you know
talking about you right you know and I
just keep saying my family is not using
me right you you calling me for the
things that I'm not good at call me for
what I'm good at I'm good at showing
up you want somebody to show up because
let me tell why I show up cuz people
need stuff to be moved and I got a truck
I don't give a damn what you trying to
move call
me I'm pulling up in the
truck put it on there I got straps and
everything if I see somebody on the side
of the road because I got chains and
I can't wait I'm just saying you
stuck I got
you put in the neutral put I'm pull the
out now my friends my friends know I'm
handy cuz they call me for the things
that I am good at I'm at this club my
partner Dre is
64 360 365 he he fluctuate between yeah
he fluctuate right 36
365 he fluctuating we I'm at this club
he there with me and I'm in there
dancing he tabed me on the shoulder I
said I said what's up boy
what's up you talking about man I'm
about to get out of here I said where
you going he said I'm about to leave
with this little old chick I'm say
[Applause]
Dre Dre don't go nowhere with that lady
Dre leave he gone I done told the man
don't go nowhere with that lady he gone
Club closed 2:00 I'm home
2:30 3:00
3:45 I get a phone call and I know he on
some cuz he going to ask me am
I sleep when I already answer the phone
like this hello I already said
that why would I not be sleep if I said
hello
he on the
phone
[Applause]
Whispering say play I said why you
Whispering why you talking so
loud cuz I'm in my house what is it
Dre man listen listen listen
listen
listen you know the lady that I left
with
I said yeah what's
up there's a
man at the
door there's a man at the door I said
Dre what difference does it make you 64
36 365 cuz you know you
[Applause]
fluctuate he say he big I say Dre how
big can he be you
64 360
365 come on boy what's up he like why
you talking so loud hey I'm in my
house I said Dre how big can this man be
he said I looked out the
people and I saw his belt buckle I said
what
what you looked out the peo and saw his
belt
buckle I said man let me let me get up
and come over here see what's going
on he off this this street called West
Park right and I get over there I get
over there and fellas you know how this
go I get over there you
ever seen somebody so big that you
looking for an apartment number and you
you know where you at and I got to that
number I looked up I said nah that can't
be right
I'm no for sure I came back and talking
loud no it ain't this ain't 320 is
it
[Applause]
woo well I called Dre I say Dre listen
to me
[Applause]
I'm outside Whispering
TR boy you ain't lying this boy big
[Applause]
boy but let me tell you let me tell you
the problem with me right the problem
with me is
that I have this
ability to get mad
about things that's not even happening
right and I can get really really mad
about something that's not happening now
I'm standing by my
truck and my partner Dre is in need and
I'm like man how how is big man going to
tell me I can't come get my partner now
this man ain't said nothing to me this
man ain't said a word to me do you
understand we ain't even exchanged no
words but I had a whole conversation to
myself going to tell me I can't get my
partner I don't even know who he talking
to let me you know something don't even
worry about let me put my thing on
me went right up them steps pardon me
big
man Dr come on out he ain't going to do
to
[Applause]
you yeah yeah yeah he ain't going to do
nothing yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's what I said nothing you know what
I'm saying yeah yeah
yeah Dre is
6'4 360 365 he
fluctuate he come out I'm 57 that man
behind me like
this come on Dre
here we going down and yeah we get in
the car I say get my truck I say Dre you
see how I back his big ass down
I sold that boy yeah yeah yeah
[Applause]
yeah so that
got to call me for what I'm good
[Applause]
at so right after that happened right
right after that happened
I'm at a family function at a family
function I told you you don't know how
people feel about you till you hear them
overt talking about you I'm I'm going to
the restroom and I walk past you know
all the young the young folk they in the
little room and I walk past one of the
little cousins say to my daughter say
Jaden you lucky your daddy tough my
daughter said
[Applause]
I come in the room I said hey hey um hey
hey
hey what's happening the the man just
said I was tough and you
said what that what that mean my
daughter daddy do I need to say I said
not only do you need to say You must say
what you talking about I said what are
you talking on all I'm going to say is
this
Walmart
Walmart Walmart Walmart Walmart I said
wait a minute are you judging
me on what happened at
Walmart
wow let me tell y'all what happened at
Walmart let me tell
youall I'm at Walmart right I'm at
Walmart okay I'm at Walmart I'm waiting
on a parking space wait on park space
right right here waiting on the park
space this young boy com in from the
wrong
direction and slide in my space I say
hey young boy man what is you doing
young boy say old school you better go
in the on now see he escalated
[Applause]
this I say what are you doing he say go
the on you you didn't escalate this
is escalation right
I say hey young boy don't make me before
I can say get out my truck the young boy
didn't took his shirt off and he's
walking towards my
truck I roll my window I said this young
boy crazy he's
crazy and I'm in the window tell him
you're crazy you're crazy you're crazy
do you know you're
crazy and he's still talking crazy at
the window I had to act like I had some
I said hey boy you better get away from
my window now all I had was a bunch of
light bills on the side of my window now
I was going to throw all them light
bills in his
face you going to have a paper cut in
your eye
[Applause]
boy so I just drive
off I just drive off just drive off
right I drive off my daughter going to
talk about daddy with your scare ass I
said I ain't see you do I ain't see
you do nothing that man was close to
your age you ain't get out of say
[Applause]
nothing is she acting like I left
Walmart I didn't leave Walmart I just
went to another parking
space he saw me in Walmart on aisle
6 say take your shirt off in Walmart and
see what happened I had that Clorox
breach spray in my head I going to Blind
this shirtless ass you going to be a
blind shirtless young is
what you about to
[Applause]
be
now like Karma right like Karma right my
daughter months later called me and said
Daddy I need to use your truck I said
for what you said cuz my dog has to go
to the doctor and I want to put him in
his kennel after he comes from the
doctor because he be a little
lethargic when he comes from the doctor
I said what type of bullsh is
that let you know your dog be a little
aric and you want to put him in the
kenel I said I have a dog too I don't
put my dog in no kennel when he lead a
doctor I just throw him in the back of
the truck that's how I know he can hula
hoop he just be back there I'm just
driving
[Applause]
I say what time does your dog have to be
at the doctor she said 6:00 a.m. I said
what he getting an MRI what type of
dog 6: a.m. can he eat at the
[Applause]
eight I said no I I'm not going to have
you packing no kenel that early in the
morning I say what I do is I'll come
over there and spend the night at your
house and then we'll take the dog in the
morning I put the k in there and we'll
go I want to stay at my daughter's house
anyway cuz in her guest bedroom is my
old bed and I want to sleep in my old
bed I'm at her house and I'm I'm knocked
out you
[Applause]
understand she coming there
daddy daddy I'm like what's
up somebody trying to break in my house
I said what
somebody's trying to break in my house
and she showed me on her phone to my I
don't know that man I said
[Applause]
damn somebody is trying to break in your
house go to your
room I got it I
got I want my
daughter to go to her room cuz I don't
want her to
see what's about to happen with
me see the thing about going back to
things that you have done in your past
um it's a transformation that happens
with with you if you've been in the
military or you've been incarcerated and
you about to go to war it is something
in you that you your um your body get
hard your your your back get
big and I told y I have the ability to
get mad about things that's not
happening and I already made up why he
trying to get in this house he going to
come in here and kill my daughter and
take her skin
off and put her skin on his
body and be walking around answering
like he my daughter hey Jaden hey what's
up yeah I already made all this up
in my head already cuz it's not going to
[Applause]
happen so I slide out this little side
door and I'm coming up the little patio
and when I get out the
gate I come through the flower bed I got
to come through the flower
bed my daughter got these little spiky
these little spiky plants you got to go
around and there stick you in the LA and
I see old boy and I know he thought them
bushes hit him I came through them
bushes bow you trying to do my he
hold on man hold on listen to me
somebody somebody just put a gun on me I
said somebody pulled a gun on you not
two people that pulled a gun on your
ass get your ass on the ground so trying
to get in my daughter house and where
the person that pulled the gun on you
where they at
oh get on your stomach what you doing
you what you got on
you boy you trying to get my daughter
I'mma blow your man what is you trying
to do boy now while I got him down I
hear some
Sirens I'm oh
[Applause]
man cuz you know I'm a convicted felon I
ain't supposed to have this
my daughter came outside I said here
take the gun and put the gun on the man
and keep the gun on the man and I went
in the house I'm
[Applause]
sleep the police out there talking to my
daughter I come out there 20 minutes
later with my robe on to my what is all
the
commotion the police say youro daughter
is so brave she captured an as salent I
said an as
[Applause]
salent they talk to me they talk to me
and they said I didn't I didn't know
nothing about it they ain't got nothing
to do with it they cleared me I'm
innocent I'm in the house
I'm in the house I'm in the kitchen
drinking
tea they talk to my daughter they talk
to my
daughter now she come in the house they
took her statement everything she come
in there crying
daddy the man triy to break up my house
Dad I would know what I would do if you
wasn't here Daddy and I'm like
this
yeah with your scare ass
I said let me let me go back let me go
back a little bit let me go back to
something I said you know a couple
months
ago when that man said that you lucky
your daddy tough you say remember okay
okay so let me let me say this I I want
you to
really digest this in your little heart
I said
my
manhood and my
pride is not attached to a Walmart
parking
space I said I'm not going to let nobody
kill me or kill nobody over a Walmart
parking
space I said if I would have died they
wouldn't even put a plaque there some
about ali died here they wouldn't even
do that
I say never judge me by something that's
not important to me you know what I'm
saying I say and if if any man you ever
with in your life attach his pride and
his manhood to these type of things this
is no man do you understand me I said
let me let me give you the uh the
real understanding that man was trying
to get in your house you are important
to me and I'm I'm do whatever to defend
you you understand me I said so don't
ever compare yourself to my love with a
wmart parking space and where's my gun
[Applause]
people judge you against things
that's not important to
you and young folk man let me tell you
man it's it's hard sometimes
helping them and you know I I have a
brother right I have a brother and he
has taken some of the joy out of my life
with helping him you know what I'm
saying no I'm talking cuz you know I'm a
real helpful person I'm type person is
this serious if you drunk and you need
somebody to come get you I would be the
one that would come get you now my
brother has used this so much that I
won't do it no more I will send somebody
cuz he he get drunk on Wednesday work
day and call you who drunk on
Wednesday call me I'm sleep more
I'm sleep the man loud I answer
the phone hello now that's how I answer
cuz I'm sleep he talk about say boy you
sleep yes that's why I
answer he said man man I'm out
being responsible I said you don't you
don't sound responsible
Darius no I'm drunk I'm tow down I'm toe
down the responsible part is me calling
[Applause]
you Darius what what what what is it man
hey man need to ride home man I'm
gone can't
drive man come get me come get me I say
darus where are you at come on man we
Brothers man you got to be a to find me
in the world we telling Kix I said what
[Applause]
because we Brothers I supposed to
know where you at in the world
Darius where have you been drinking at
man lot of places lot of
places been drunk all over the
city what is the last place I don't
know where I'm at I said man put
the phone on FaceTime so I can see where
you at the boy puts the phone on
FaceTime he just got it on his forehead
all I can see is his forehead
turn the phone around Darius he got the
phone in the
algae I said okay I see where you at I'm
on the way did y'all y'all hear what I
said I am on the way that means me that
means me I'm coming I pull up to the
spot he come out Tippy toeing like he
don't know who I am talking about is
somebody here for Darius get your ass in
this car I'm not your lift some about
this somebody here for Darius like you
don't know my
[Applause]
face the worst thing in the
world is to be in a car with somebody
that's
drunk and you are not
drunk you in the car this is me in the
car I'm
he over
there
Darius don't say nothing to
[Applause]
me just sit over there and be quiet he
over there I ain't I ain't even saying
nothing he I'm just sitting here I'm
sitting
here I said man go to bed go to sleep
dog just don't say nothing to
me I have to to cut the radio off
because he's trying to sing all the
songs to me he singing to
me last straw htown come on he over
there body rocking lock in the uh-uh off
off no rocking nobody rocking no
knocking no nothing off off I want to
pull it out the wall
off go to sleep
[Applause]
we get to his house right we get to his
house it's about 12 Steps From The
Curve to his house I wake him up I say
hey hey you home come on come get out
let's go he going to wake up tell me man
what type of is
this you ain't going to walk a damn so
in distress to you are not a damn get
out my house get out of here
no damn Damsel in
[Applause]
Distress people man now you know what's
crazy I got old people in my family and
you have to listen to the elderly now
elderly they've been around a long time
that you can learn things from Elder you
know I just learn that you can return
produce had no
idea clueless to it I'm and in first of
all I'm too nosy cuz grocery store is my
favorite place I'm coming out the
grocery store rolling through the
parking lot I see this old cat with a
watermelon in his hand coming towards
the grocery store
here and I say old school you can Dro
your watermelon in the paring lot he
talk about nah this about
to go back I said
what I said but it's open he said about
I don't give a it ain't
[Applause]
sweet
what they can afford to have a
watermelon that's not sweet I can't I
said I turned my basket around I want to
see this I want to see it I need to
see with my own
eyes I'm back in the store
old school wasting no time Old School
come in with the watermelon go straight
to customer
service put it down and say that's
y'alls I said that's
y'alls no proof of purchase no
receipt you could have found that water
man in the park lot that's
[Music]
y'alls old school is in the produce
section cutting watermelons
open no that's bad too yeah
and that would even worse y'all got a
whole bch of badass watermelon
here oh that's it right
there that man grabb that Waterman and
walk P coule sir we good ain't
we most amazing thing I ever saw that he
you he was 80 you got to be 80 years old
to do that
I'm tell you got to be old to do it I'm
trying to tell you I get
home my peaches ain't
sweet just saw
this I'm back in the
store that's
[Applause]
y'alls I'm in the produce
section biting peaches
[Applause]
you got to be old to do it you got to be
old you got to be old
[Applause]
even though I'm not the hand this
person I do give good
advice I do give great advice now
especially to young
men I've been
through I've been through a lot so I
give good advice I tell young people all
the time listen to the elders because
for some reason being 50 I'm the last we
are the last you in your 50 you the last
of the listening generation you last of
the listeners you're the last I'm
talking about cuz see and I'm talking
about listening not the
talk it's a difference between listening
and listening to the talk see I listen
like this when you talking to me I'm
like
this all the information people that's
over 50 I mean that's under 50 this they
listen they listen like this let me I
ain't trying to interrupt
[Applause]
you you're really not hearing everything
and they think that they the same as you
they think they the same as you you 50
they 40 you you're not the same you
don't even know the same that I
know so I tell young men listen to me
find you some good Elders to listen to
because you don't know everything cuz
it's a difference young men that's in
here just ask you a
question have you ever walked into a
restroom and saw a man at the Ural with
his whole ass
out whole ass out
[Applause]
first time I ever see
this I'm 27 years
old and I'm I'm I'm and I ain't got to
even be like this I walk in the man at
the Ural whole ass out and I'm 27 just
to much I come in there God damn old
school you got your whole ass out I see
laugh and just drawing attention to
it cuz I'm young and
foolish I don't even know how this
happens now I kept living
[Applause]
right 27 your bladder
tight you can pee once a month if you
want
[Applause]
to once you get over
40 if you even think think about peeing
you got to
go right you got to get out of there I'm
44 years
old and I'm disrespecting my
bladder cuz I'm doing what my
grandmother said running my mouth you
know that's what she used to call you in
there running your mouth I'm talking to
somebody running my mouth and while I
was running my mouth my bladder told me
to my bladder said hey
boy you better get
somewhere I sat there and kept running
my
mouth and man I tell you after that
conversation was over I took a
turnaround step and said oh wait a
[Applause]
minute it's coming out wait a minute
wait a
[Applause]
minute I'm in here leaking wait a minute
wait I had to do them little steps that
my daughter be doing when she trying to
get to the bathroom
I get in the bathroom I get in the
bathroom and my belt won't come
off now you can on it River Dance for so
[Applause]
long I said oh this about to come
out
[Applause]
just sitting there with my whole ass out
just whole ass
[Applause]
out and like the law of
karma this young boy walked in the
restroom and said God damn old school
you got your whole ass up
I said keep
living my name is Ali sadik man
[Applause]
[Music]
a
m
[Music]